<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.2.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://naem-j.github.io/portfolio/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://naem-j.github.io/portfolio/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2024-02-15T21:14:13-08:00</updated><id>https://naem-j.github.io/portfolio/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Technical Writing Portfolio</title><subtitle>Welcome to my technical writing portfolio. The following selection of samples represent or demonstrate different types of documents, tools, and skills I&apos;ve used to communicate technical information. However, the samples are limited to publically available documents or redacted examples. To learn more about the context, process, and tools used to create each sample, select the appropriate card below.
</subtitle><author><name>Jeff Naemura</name></author><entry><title type="html">IFU</title><link href="https://naem-j.github.io/portfolio/ifu" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="IFU" /><published>2024-02-15T00:00:00-08:00</published><updated>2024-02-15T00:00:00-08:00</updated><id>https://naem-j.github.io/portfolio/ifu</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://naem-j.github.io/portfolio/ifu">&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;images/905-2040-002_E.pdf&quot;&gt;IFU Sample&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;summary&quot;&gt;Summary&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is an example of an IFU or DFU document (as defined by the FDA, EU, and IEC standards) for assisting ophthalmic surgical procedures. The company that was developing the device was bought by my employer and existing documentation needed to be drastically reworked and assimilated into our company standards. The document was printed in a 3-ring binder and supplied with the device.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The target audience for this document were external ophthalmic surgeons, their medical staff, and responsible organizations (for example, hospitals and their Facilities personnel or IT departments). These groups ranged from non-technical to technical.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;responsibilities&quot;&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My responsibilities were to collaborate with the remaining engineers, regulatory assurance personnel, and other SMEs from the original company to determine the scope and needed effort for the documentation project and then create and streamline content to meet Alcon and external regulatory standards (for example, FDA CFR, EU MDR, and IEC 60601-1 standards).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I used InDesign to create a template based on guidelines discussed with the other members of the Alcon Technical Publications team and laid out content in that application. I was also responsible for all screenshots and illustrations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was the only technical writer on the project and drove the project from company assimilation to release. I also submitted documents into the company product lifecycle management tool and drove the review and approval cycle until full approval. After that, I also coordinated with the print vendor to deliver finished printed copies and verify the quality.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;tools-used&quot;&gt;Tools Used&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Adobe Acrobat Pro&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Adobe Illustrator&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Adobe InDesign&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Adobe Photoshop&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;PTC Windchill&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</content><author><name>Jeff Naemura</name></author><category term="IFU" /><category term="DFU" /><category term="instructions for use" /><category term="directions for use" /><summary type="html">IFU Sample</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Knowledge Base</title><link href="https://naem-j.github.io/portfolio/knowledge-base" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Knowledge Base" /><published>2023-01-16T00:00:00-08:00</published><updated>2023-01-16T00:00:00-08:00</updated><id>https://naem-j.github.io/portfolio/knowledge-base</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://naem-j.github.io/portfolio/knowledge-base">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;images/confluence_sample.png&quot; alt=&quot;Knowledge Base Page Sample&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;summary&quot;&gt;Summary&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is an example of an internal knowledge base article written for the technical writing team to clone a remote repository. In general, the knowledge base was only for the technical writing team to share knowledge on R&amp;amp;D projects, writing best practices, and procedures not defined in company SOPs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Most of the remote technical writing team did not have any experience with MadCap Flare or Git. However, the company was moving use both.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;responsibilities&quot;&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My responsibilities were to collaborate on the information architecture of entire knowledge base and populate most content. The article in the example used a combination of steps, code samples, and an animated gif demonstrating the steps.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;tools-used&quot;&gt;Tools Used&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Atlassian Confluence&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;TechSmith Snagit&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</content><author><name>Jeff Naemura</name></author><category term="knowledge base" /><category term="documentation" /><category term="confluence" /><category term="snagit" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">FAQ</title><link href="https://naem-j.github.io/portfolio/faq" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="FAQ" /><published>2022-12-30T00:00:00-08:00</published><updated>2022-12-30T00:00:00-08:00</updated><id>https://naem-j.github.io/portfolio/faq</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://naem-j.github.io/portfolio/faq">&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;images/faq.pdf&quot;&gt;FAQ Sample&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;summary&quot;&gt;Summary&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is an example of an FAQ that details network requirements and security features of medical devices that can be set up to share data over the customer network. The format answers specific questions that are often asked in questionnaire form by prospective customers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The target audience is customer IT departments and field service engineers. These groups are highly technical.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;tools-used&quot;&gt;Tools Used&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Adobe Illustrator&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Microsoft Word&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</content><author><name>Jeff Naemura</name></author><category term="faq" /><category term="frequently asked questions" /><category term="answers" /><category term="documentation" /><category term="microsoft" /><category term="word" /><summary type="html">FAQ Sample</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Illustrations</title><link href="https://naem-j.github.io/portfolio/illustrations" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Illustrations" /><published>2022-03-12T00:00:00-08:00</published><updated>2022-03-12T00:00:00-08:00</updated><id>https://naem-j.github.io/portfolio/illustrations</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://naem-j.github.io/portfolio/illustrations">&lt;h2 id=&quot;summary&quot;&gt;Summary&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The following samples are vector-based illustrations that portray different kinds of information: for example, hardware interconnections or the flow of data.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;images/device_iso.svg&quot; alt=&quot;Isometric Projection&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Isometric Projection&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;images/camera_installation.svg&quot; alt=&quot;Exploded View Diagram&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Exploded View Diagram&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;images/datafusion.svg&quot; alt=&quot;Signal Flow&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Signal Flow&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;tools-used&quot;&gt;Tools Used&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Adobe Illustrator&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;CreoView&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;TechSmith Snagit&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</content><author><name>Jeff Naemura</name></author><category term="illustrations" /><category term="drawings" /><category term="vector" /><category term="adobe" /><category term="illustrator" /><summary type="html">Summary</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Style Guide</title><link href="https://naem-j.github.io/portfolio/style-guide" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Style Guide" /><published>2021-07-10T00:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2021-07-10T00:00:00-07:00</updated><id>https://naem-j.github.io/portfolio/style-guide</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://naem-j.github.io/portfolio/style-guide">&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;images/style_guide_redacted.pdf&quot;&gt;Style Guide Sample&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;summary&quot;&gt;Summary&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These excerpts are examples of a comprehensive style guide I created for the Technical Publications team. During a Lean Six Sigma Green Belt project I planned and implemented, this was identified as a gap in mistake proofing our development and review process. The project required standardizing both basic and deep writing topics as well as defining how visual aids should appear. The style guide worked in conjunction with a preparation and review checklist to ensure authors and reviewers were held to the same expectations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The style guide is an internal document, so the full version is not available publicly. However, the excerpts demonstrate the level of detail required to educate and ensure the responsibility of other technical writers to each other and their writing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;responsibilities&quot;&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My responsibilities included educating other technical writers in basic grammar and punctuation rules, identifying subjective writing topics to standardize, and providing guidance on best practices for visual aid design and maintenance. For reference, the style guide covered the following high-level topics:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Parts of speech&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Syntax (including use of phrases, flow, and complexity)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Language (including clarity, jargon, formality, and consistency)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Spelling and formatting (including capitalization, formatting numbers, and formatting other types of terms)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Punctuation&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Styles (including whitespace and alignment manipulation)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Visual aids (including scope, callouts, and leader lines)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;target-audience&quot;&gt;Target Audience&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Internal technical writers (authors and reviewers)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;External technical writers&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Technical Publications manager&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;tools&quot;&gt;Tools&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Microsoft Word&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Jeff Naemura</name></author><category term="style guide" /><category term="writing" /><category term="visual aids" /><category term="illustrations" /><category term="drawings" /><category term="images" /><category term="microsoft" /><category term="word" /><summary type="html">Style Guide Sample</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Checklists</title><link href="https://naem-j.github.io/portfolio/checklists" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Checklists" /><published>2021-01-25T00:00:00-08:00</published><updated>2021-01-25T00:00:00-08:00</updated><id>https://naem-j.github.io/portfolio/checklists</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://naem-j.github.io/portfolio/checklists">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;images/prep_checklist.png&quot; alt=&quot;Preparation Checklist&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Preparation Checklist for Authors to Complete before Peer Review&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;images/review_checklist.png&quot; alt=&quot;Review Checklist&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Review Checklist for Reviewers to Complete during Peer Review&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;summary&quot;&gt;Summary&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These excerpts are examples of two checklists I made to improve the internal review cycle lead time. They worked in conjunction with each other as well as the department style guide. These two checklists were identified as a gap in mistake proofing our development and review process during a Lean Six Sigma Green Belt project I planned and implemented. Prior to the implementation of these checklists and style guide, review cycles were repeated many times due to disagreements between writers on non-standardized topics or disagreements on the responsibilities of the author and reviewer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The checklists are an internal documents, so the full versions are not available publicly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;responsibilities&quot;&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My responsibilities included creating two checklists: one for the author to ensure work is edited and complete before sending it for review and one for the reviewer to ensure work complies with the style guide and identify any gaps in the style guide coverage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;target-audience&quot;&gt;Target Audience&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Internal technical writers (authors and reviewers)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;External technical writers&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Technical Publications manager&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;tools&quot;&gt;Tools&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Microsoft Word&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Jeff Naemura</name></author><category term="preparation" /><category term="review" /><category term="checklists" /><category term="microsoft" /><category term="word" /><summary type="html">Preparation Checklist for Authors to Complete before Peer Review</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Theory of Operation</title><link href="https://naem-j.github.io/portfolio/theory-of-ops" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Theory of Operation" /><published>2020-07-20T00:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2020-07-20T00:00:00-07:00</updated><id>https://naem-j.github.io/portfolio/theory-of-ops</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://naem-j.github.io/portfolio/theory-of-ops">&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;images/906-2040-002_D_theory.pdf&quot;&gt;Theory of Operation Sample&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;summary&quot;&gt;Summary&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is an excerpt from a service manual that details the theory of operation of the various system components. The section is intended to provide detailed explanations of how the various components work, their feature set, and how they interconnect.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;responsibilities&quot;&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was responsible for the entire document, but regarding this section specifically, my responsibilities included distilling relevant information from technical description files, and writing the text, and creating the block diagrams. The visual and writing styles were in adherence with the style guide.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;target-audience&quot;&gt;Target Audience&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Field service engineers or technicians&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Technical support&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;tools&quot;&gt;Tools&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Adobe InDesign&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Adobe Illustrator&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</content><author><name>Jeff Naemura</name></author><category term="faq" /><category term="frequently asked questions" /><category term="answers" /><category term="documentation" /><category term="microsoft" /><category term="word" /><summary type="html">Theory of Operation Sample</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Web User Guide</title><link href="https://naem-j.github.io/portfolio/web-user-guide" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Web User Guide" /><published>2020-07-20T00:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2020-07-20T00:00:00-07:00</updated><id>https://naem-j.github.io/portfolio/web-user-guide</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://naem-j.github.io/portfolio/web-user-guide">&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://naem-j.github.io/web-doc-sample/&quot;&gt;Web-based User Guide Sample&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;summary&quot;&gt;Summary&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This sample of a web document was converted from a printed user guide I authored. The original document was intended to be provided as a printed book with hardware and satisfy EU and IEC instructions for use and FDA directions for use definitions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The document is provided in its original PDF form on the company website for “labeling,” but it has since been updated. The web sample coincides with the last PDF revision I authored.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;responsibilities&quot;&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The product was acquired by my company, but documentation for it was written and organized by a quality engineer that had since left the company. One of my first responsibilities was to coordinate with an R&amp;amp;D engineer for the acquired company and completely rewrite the document.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ultimately, I was responsible for writing most of the content (with very little content reused from the original document), reorganizing the topics to better match FDA guidelines, and assimilating the document to the company branding. I also drew vector-based illustrations of hardware in isometric and orthographic projections based on CAD drawings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The original PDF was reviewed informally with SMEs and other writers and formally through PTC Windchill (CCMS). Reviews were performed primarily with PDF comments and changes were justified in the CMS with company-defined “redlines.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the web-based version, I parsed the content from a binary file (Adobe InDesign) into modular topics (markdown files). I utilized a free Hugo theme to create the layout and published it to GitHub. Content was created with markdown, HTML, and CSS. Styles were predominately provided by the theme creator, but slightly manipulated using TOML and CSS.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;target-audience&quot;&gt;Target Audience&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Ophthalmic surgeons and their medical staff&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;IT departments&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Responsible organizations (owners of the equipment)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;tools&quot;&gt;Tools&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Atom&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Adobe Illustrator&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Adobe Photoshop&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Git&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;GitHub&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Hugo&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;NOTE: For the original PDF, I also used Adobe InDesign, Microsoft SharePoint, and PTC Windchill.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Jeff Naemura</name></author><category term="user guide" /><category term="procedures" /><category term="documentation" /><category term="manual" /><category term="IFU" /><category term="DFU" /><category term="static site generator" /><category term="hugo" /><category term="photoshop" /><category term="illustrator" /><category term="atom" /><summary type="html">Web-based User Guide Sample</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Service Label</title><link href="https://naem-j.github.io/portfolio/service-label" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Service Label" /><published>2020-04-27T00:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2020-04-27T00:00:00-07:00</updated><id>https://naem-j.github.io/portfolio/service-label</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://naem-j.github.io/portfolio/service-label">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;images/label_workspace.png&quot; alt=&quot;Service Label Sample&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;XML data set of localized content that matches Illustrator variables&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;summary&quot;&gt;Summary&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is a screenshot of the workspace in Adobe Illustrator I used to generate a service label that needed to be translated and localized in more than 60 regions around the world. With the help of feedback from the Global Technical Services department and global affiliates, I designed the label to display contact information and the next service date for the equipment. Another engineer determined the print vendor, materials, and location for the labels.
These labels encouraged global customers to contact the company to schedule preventive maintenance. However, global field service engineers needed to order them and fill in appropriate dates.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To support so many regions and languages, I created variables to display different parts of the label in a specific language and with the appropriate contact information. The Data Set drop-down menu in the previous example shows a selection of different regions, each with a unique identification number, to choose from. The actual text or numbers to display in the variables were managed in a separate XML file I created and associated with the variables shown in the previous example.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To generate the labels, I created an Illustrator action to batch output each localized label in the data set in .pdf and .ai format. This process helped improve the time to generate the labels, ensure accuracy, and update parts of them (if necessary).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;responsibilities&quot;&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My responsibilities were to design the label from a layout standpoint. I recommended creating a template to batch output the labels using XML to manage the actual content. However, to do this I had to ensure the design would fit text in other languages that could be significantly longer than others. I was also responsible for generating the version-controlled artwork file (shown in the previous example).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The actual translations and localization of text and contact information was done by global affiliates via email. After they were provided, I added them to the XML file under a new record with a provided ID number.
The Technical Service and Alcon logos were created by another team and not subject to localization. Likewise, the color scheme followed Alcon branding guidelines.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The size of the label were also determined in conjunction with me, the print vendor, and the engineer responsible for choosing the vendor and materials. Ultimately, the size was picked as a minimal size needed to support the longest text requirements and that provided the most cost savings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;tools-used&quot;&gt;Tools Used&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Adobe Illustrator&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Adobe Dreamweaver and Notepad++&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</content><author><name>Jeff Naemura</name></author><category term="label" /><category term="sticker" /><category term="service" /><category term="adobe" /><category term="illustrator" /><category term="xml" /><summary type="html">XML data set of localized content that matches Illustrator variables</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Script</title><link href="https://naem-j.github.io/portfolio/script" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Script" /><published>2019-09-25T00:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2019-09-25T00:00:00-07:00</updated><id>https://naem-j.github.io/portfolio/script</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://naem-j.github.io/portfolio/script">&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;images/video_script.pdf&quot;&gt;Video Script Sample&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;summary&quot;&gt;Summary&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This excerpt is an example of a script I created for a video demonstrating how to pack and transport medical equipment in custom containers and company vehicles. The script is an internal document, so the full version is not available.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;responsibilities&quot;&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My responsibilities included converting a procedure document into a script for either an internal video creator or third-party vendor. I worked with the designer of the custom containers and author of the procedure to write the script. However, I did not create the video.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;target-audience&quot;&gt;Target Audience&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Video creator and editor&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Sales&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Marketing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;tools&quot;&gt;Tools&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Microsoft Word&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Jeff Naemura</name></author><category term="script" /><category term="video" /><category term="microsoft" /><category term="word" /><summary type="html">Video Script Sample</summary></entry></feed>